



export const db = [
    {
        topicName: "Common java methods",
        entries: [
            {
                id: 1,
                question: "string.charAt(index):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Returns the character at a specific index"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 2,
                question: "string.length():",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Returns the length of the string"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 3,
                question: "string.substring(start, end):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Extracts a portion of the string"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 4,
                question: "string1.equals(string2):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Compares two strings for equality"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 5,
                question: "string.toLowerCase():",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Converts the string to lowercase"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 6,
                question: "string.toUpperCase():",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Converts the string to uppercase"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 7,
                question: "string.trim():",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Removes leading and trailing whitespace"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 8,
                question: "string.replace(oldChar, newChar):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Replaces characters in the string"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 9,
                question: "int number = (int) doubleValue:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Manually converts a larger type to a smaller type"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 10,
                question: "double largerType = intValue:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Automatically converts a smaller type to a larger type"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 11,
                question: "Integer.parseInt(string):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Converts a string to an integer"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 12,
                question: "Integer.valueOf(intValue):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Converts a primitive to a wrapper type"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 13,
                question: "Integer.toString(intValue):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Converts a primitive to a string"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 14,
                question: "Math.abs(value):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Returns the absolute value"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 15,
                question: "Math.sqrt(value):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Returns the square root of a number"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 16,
                question: "Math.pow(base, exponent):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Returns the value of base raised to the power of exponent"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 17,
                question: "Math.max(num1, num2):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Returns the larger of two numbers"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 18,
                question: "Math.min(num1, num2):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Returns the smaller of two numbers"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 19,
                question: "Math.random():",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Returns a random number between 0.0 and 1.0"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 20,
                question: "Math.round(value):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Rounds a decimal value to the nearest integer"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 21,
                question: "array.length:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Returns the size of the array"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 22,
                question: "Arrays.sort(array):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Sorts the elements of the array"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 23,
                question: "Arrays.binarySearch(array, key):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Searches for a key in a sorted array"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 24,
                question: "Arrays.copyOf(array, newSize):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: [
                    "Copies an array to a new array with a specified size",
                ],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 25,
                question: "Arrays.toString(array):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Returns a string representation of the array"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 26,
                question: "Arrays.fill(array, value):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Fills an array with a specific value"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 27,
                question: "Arrays.equals(array1, array2):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Compares two arrays for equality"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        topicName: "Command Line Utilities",
        entries: [
            {
                id: 28,
                question: "mvn:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage Java projects with Maven."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 29,
                question: "npm:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage JavaScript packages and dependencies."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 30,
                question: "gradle:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To build and manage software projects, often Java-based."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 31,
                question: "pip:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage Python packages and libraries."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 32,
                question: "composer:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage PHP project dependencies."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 33,
                question: "gem:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage Ruby packages (gems)."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 34,
                question: "yarn:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage JavaScript dependencies, similar to npm."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 35,
                question: "cargo:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage Rust packages and projects."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 36,
                question: "go:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage Go modules and dependencies."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 37,
                question: "brew:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage software packages on macOS."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 38,
                question: "docker:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage containerized applications."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 39,
                question: "kubectl:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage Kubernetes clusters and resources."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 40,
                question: "terraform:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage infrastructure as code across clouds."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 41,
                question: "ansible:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To automate IT tasks and manage configurations."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 42,
                question: "vagrant:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage virtual development environments."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 43,
                question: "make:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To automate build processes in software development."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 44,
                question: "npx:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To run Node.js packages without installing them globally."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 45,
                question: "git:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage version control for source code."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 46,
                question: "ssh:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To connect securely to remote systems."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 47,
                question: "curl:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To transfer data from or to a server using various protocols."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 48,
                question: "wget:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To download files from the web (alternative to curl)."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 49,
                question: "zsh/bash:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Shells for interacting with the operating system."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 50,
                question: "rsync:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To synchronize files between systems."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 51,
                question: "ffmpeg:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manipulate and convert multimedia files (audio/video)."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 52,
                question: "tmux:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To manage terminal sessions and split panes."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 53,
                question: "htop:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To monitor system resource usage interactively."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 54,
                question: "jq:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["To parse and manipulate JSON data from the command line."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 55,
                question: "aws/az/gcloud:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: [
                    "CLI tools for managing AWS, Azure, and Google Cloud resources.",
                ],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 56,
                question: "python/node/ruby:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: [
                    "Interpreters for running respective programming languages directly.",
                ],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        topicName: "Git",
        entries: [
            {
                id: 57,
                question: "File logs:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git log -p <file>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 58,
                question: "Differences:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git diff"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 59,
                question: "Stash changes:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git stash"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 60,
                question: "Apply stashed changes:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git stash apply"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 61,
                question: "Reset to specific commit:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git reset --hard <commit-hash>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 62,
                question: "Revert a commit:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git revert <commit-hash>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 63,
                question: "Fetch changes of repo:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git fetch"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 64,
                question: "Pull changes of repo:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git pull"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 65,
                question: "Push changes to repo:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git push origin <branch-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 66,
                question: "Delete branch:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git branch -d <branch-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 67,
                question: "Merge branch:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git merge <branch-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 68,
                question: "Create and switch branch:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git checkout -b <branch-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 69,
                question: "Switch branch:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git checkout <branch-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 70,
                question: "Create new branch:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git branch <branch-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 71,
                question: "View commit history:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git log"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 72,
                question: "Commit changes:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ['git commit -m "commit message"'],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 73,
                question: "Stage changes (specific file):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git add <file>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 74,
                question: "Stage all changes:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git add ."],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 75,
                question: "View repo status:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git status"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 76,
                question: "Clone repository:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git clone <repository-url>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 77,
                question: "Initialize repository:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["git init"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        topicName: "Shell/Bash/Kernel",
        entries: [
            {
                id: 78,
                question: "Clear terminal:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["clear"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 79,
                question: "Install something:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["install"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 80,
                question: "Super user do:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["sudo"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 81,
                question: "What's working on a port:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["sudo lsof -i :portnr"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 82,
                question: "Stop what's working on this port:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["kill -9 PID"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 83,
                question: "Kill a process:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["kill <PID>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 84,
                question: "View running processes:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["ps aux"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 85,
                question: "System information:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["uname -a"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 86,
                question: "Kernel messages:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["dmesg"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 87,
                question: "Disk usage:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["df -h"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 88,
                question: "Memory usage:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["free -h"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 89,
                question: "Processes and resource usage:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["top"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 90,
                question: "Display memory usage:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["vm_start"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 91,
                question: "List files:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["ls"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 92,
                question: "Change directory:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["cd <directory>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 93,
                question: "Show current directory:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["pwd"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 94,
                question: "Create a new directory:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["mkdir"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 95,
                question: "Remove a file or directory:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["rm"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 96,
                question: "Copy files or directories:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["cp"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 97,
                question: "Move and rename file or directory:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["mv"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 98,
                question: "Create new file:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["touch"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 99,
                question: "Open files or applications:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["open"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 100,
                question: "Change file permissions:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["chmod <permissions> <file>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 101,
                question: "Change file ownership:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["chown"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 102,
                question: "Access or modify user defaults:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["defaults"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 103,
                question: "Check connectivity:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["ping <hostname or IP>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 104,
                question: "Download file:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["curl -O <url>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 105,
                question: "Get headers only:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["curl -I <url>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 106,
                question: "Transfer file:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["wget <url>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 107,
                question: "Show IP configuration:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["ifconfig (or ip a on newer systems)"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 108,
                question: "Open remote shell:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["ssh user@<hostname>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 109,
                question: "View network connections:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["netstat -tuln"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 110,
                question: "Traceroute:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["traceroute <hostname>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 111,
                question: "DNS lookup:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["nslookup <hostname>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 112,
                question: "Show active TCP connections:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["ss -t"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 113,
                question: "Encryption:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["echo -n password | base64"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 114,
                question: "Decryption:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["base64 -D"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        topicName: "PowerShell",
        entries: [
            // Files & Directory
            {
                id: 115,
                question: "List files and directories in the current location:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-ChildItem"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 116,
                question: "Copy files or directories:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Copy-Item"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 117,
                question: "Move or rename files or directories:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Move-Item"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 118,
                question: "Delete files or directories:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Remove-Item"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // System Information
            {
                id: 119,
                question: "List running processes:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-Process"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 120,
                question: "List installed services:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-Service"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 121,
                question: "Retrieve system information using Windows Management Instrumentation (WMI):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-WmiObject"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // User and Group Management
            {
                id: 122,
                question: "List local users:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-LocalUser"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 123,
                question: "Create a new local user:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["New-LocalUser"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 124,
                question: "Add a user to a local group:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Add-LocalGroupMember"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // Networking
            {
                id: 125,
                question: "Ping a remote host to test network connectivity:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Test-Connection"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 126,
                question: "Test network connectivity and troubleshoot network issues:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Test-NetConnection"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // Registry Operations
            {
                id: 127,
                question: "Get values from the Windows Registry:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-ItemProperty"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 128,
                question: "Set values in the Windows Registry:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Set-ItemProperty"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // File Content Manipulation
            {
                id: 129,
                question: "Read the content of files:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-Content"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 130,
                question: "Write content to files:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Set-Content"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 131,
                question: "Search for text patterns in files:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Select-String"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // Package Management
            {
                id: 132,
                question: "List installed software packages:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-Package"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 133,
                question: "Install software packages:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Install-Package"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 134,
                question: "Uninstall software packages:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Uninstall-Package"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // Security and Permissions
            {
                id: 135,
                question: "Retrieve access control lists (ACLs) for files and directories:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-Acl"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 136,
                question: "Set ACLs to manage permissions:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Set-Acl"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // Remote Management
            {
                id: 137,
                question: "Start an interactive session on a remote computer:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Enter-PSSession"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 138,
                question: "Run commands on remote computers:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Invoke-Command"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 139,
                question: "Copy files to a remote session:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Copy-Item -ToSession"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // Environmental Variables
            {
                id: 140,
                question: "List environment variables:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-ChildItem Env"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 141,
                question: "Set or modify environment variables:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Set-Item Env"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        topicName: "Azure PowerShell",
        entries: [
            // General
            {
                id: 142,
                question: "Start PowerShell:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["pwsh"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 143,
                question: "Create a PowerShell script:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["nano MyScript.ps1"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 144,
                question: "Get short date:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["date"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 145,
                question: "Get AZ CLI version:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["az version"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 146,
                question: "Upgrade AZ CLI:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["az upgrade"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 147,
                question: "AZ CLI interactive mode (command declarations):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["az interactive"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 148,
                question: "Exit the interactive mode:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["exit"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 149,
                question: "Create a virtual machine in Azure CLI:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["az vm create"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // Resource Management
            {
                id: 150,
                question: "Log in to your Azure account:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Login-AzAccount"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 151,
                question: "List resource groups:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-AzResourceGroup"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 152,
                question: "Create a new resource group:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["New-AzResourceGroup"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 153,
                question: "List resources in a resource group or subscription:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-AzResource"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 154,
                question: "Create a new resource in a resource group:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["New-AzResource"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 155,
                question: "Delete a resource:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Remove-AzResource"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // Virtual Machines
            {
                id: 156,
                question: "Create a new virtual machine:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["New-AzVM"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 157,
                question: "Start a virtual machine:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Start-AzVM"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 158,
                question: "Stop a virtual machine:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Stop-AzVM"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 159,
                question: "Restart a virtual machine:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Restart-AzVM"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 160,
                question: "Update the configuration of a virtual machine:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Update-AzVM"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // Azure Storage
            {
                id: 161,
                question: "Create a new storage account:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["New-AzStorageAccount"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 162,
                question: "List storage accounts:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-AzStorageAccount"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 163,
                question: "Create a new storage container:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["New-AzStorageContainer"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 164,
                question: "List storage containers:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-AzStorageContainer"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 165,
                question: "Upload a file to a storage container:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Set-AzStorageBlobContent"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // App Service
            {
                id: 166,
                question: "Create a new Azure Web App:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["New-AzWebApp"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 167,
                question: "List Azure Web Apps:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-AzWebApp"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 168,
                question: "Deploy a local app to an Azure Web App:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Publish-AzWebApp"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // Azure SQL Database
            {
                id: 169,
                question: "Create a new Azure SQL Server:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["New-AzSqlServer"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 170,
                question: "Create a new Azure SQL Database:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["New-AzSqlDatabase"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 171,
                question: "List Azure SQL Databases:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-AzSqlDatabase"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // Azure Virtual Network
            {
                id: 172,
                question: "Create a new virtual network:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["New-AzVirtualNetwork"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 173,
                question: "Create a subnet configuration:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["New-AzVirtualNetworkSubnetConfig"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 174,
                question: "List virtual networks:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-AzVirtualNetwork"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // Azure Key Vault
            {
                id: 175,
                question: "Create a new Azure Key Vault:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["New-AzKeyVault"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 176,
                question: "List Azure Key Vaults:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-AzKeyVault"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 177,
                question: "Set a secret in an Azure Key Vault:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Set-AzKeyVaultSecret"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // Azure Active Directory
            {
                id: 178,
                question: "Create a new Azure Active Directory (AD) service principal:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["New-AzADServicePrincipal"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 179,
                question: "List Azure AD service principals:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-AzADServicePrincipal"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },

            // Azure Resource Locks
            {
                id: 180,
                question: "Create a new resource lock:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["New-AzResourceLock"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 181,
                question: "List resource locks:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Get-AzResourceLock"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 182,
                question: "Remove a resource lock:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Remove-AzResourceLock"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        topicName: "MacOS Commands",
        entries: [
            // General Commands
            {
                id: 183,
                question: "Select all:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-A"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 184,
                question: "Copy:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-C"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 185,
                question: "Duplicate selected item or Bookmark page in Safari:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-D"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 186,
                question: "Eject:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-E"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 187,
                question: "Undo:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-Z"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 188,
                question: "Find in Finder:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-F"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 189,
                question: "Hide:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-H"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 190,
                question: "Show Info:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-I"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 191,
                question: "View Options:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-J"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 192,
                question: "Connect to Server:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-K"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 193,
                question: "Create an alias:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-L"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 194,
                question: "Minimize Window:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-M"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 195,
                question: "Open a new Finder Window or New Document:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-N"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 196,
                question: "Open:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-O"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 197,
                question: "Print:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-P"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 198,
                question: "Quit an app:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-Q"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 199,
                question: "Reload page or Rotate image:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-R"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 200,
                question: "Save:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-S"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 201,
                question: "Open a new tab:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-T"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 202,
                question: "Quick Look:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-Y"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 203,
                question: "Paste:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-V"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 204,
                question: "Close Window:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-W"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 205,
                question: "Cut:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Command-X"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 206,
                question: "Log out of macOS user account (Shift-Command-Q):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: [
                    "Shift-Command-Q: Log out after confirmation",
                    "Option-Shift-Command-Q: Log out immediately",
                ],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 207,
                question: "Open the Computer window:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Shift-Command-C"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 208,
                question: "Open the desktop folder:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Shift-Command-D"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 209,
                question: "Open the Recents window:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Shift-Command-F"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 210,
                question: "Open a Go to Folder window:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Shift-Command-G"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 211,
                question: "Open the Home folder:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Shift-Command-H"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 212,
                question: "Empty the Trash without confirmation:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Option-Shift-Command-Delete"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        topicName: "Linux Commands",
        entries: [
            {
                id: 213,
                question: "List files and directories:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["ls"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 214,
                question: "Change directory:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["cd <directory>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 215,
                question: "Display current directory:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["pwd"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 216,
                question: "Create a new directory:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["mkdir <directory-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 217,
                question: "Remove a file:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["rm <file-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 218,
                question: "Remove a directory recursively:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["rm -r <directory-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 219,
                question: "Copy a file:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["cp <source> <destination>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 220,
                question: "Move or rename a file or directory:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["mv <source> <destination>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 221,
                question: "Search for a file or directory:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["find <path> -name <name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 222,
                question: "Display file content:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["cat <file-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 223,
                question: "Display file content with paging:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["less <file-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 224,
                question: "Create an empty file:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["touch <file-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 225,
                question: "Display running processes:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["ps"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 226,
                question: "Kill a process by PID:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["kill <PID>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 227,
                question: "Check disk space usage:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["df -h"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 228,
                question: "Check memory usage:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["free -h"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 229,
                question: "Search for a string in files:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["grep '<pattern>' <file>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 230,
                question: "Show network configuration:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["ifconfig (deprecated, use ip a)"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 231,
                question: "Show routing table:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["route -n"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 232,
                question: "Ping a host:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["ping <host-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 233,
                question: "Download files from a URL:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["wget <URL>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 234,
                question: "Transfer data from or to a URL:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["curl <URL>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 235,
                question: "Switch to superuser mode:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["sudo su"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 236,
                question: "Change file permissions:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["chmod <permissions> <file>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 237,
                question: "Change file ownership:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["chown <owner>:<group> <file>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 238,
                question: "Compress a file with gzip:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["gzip <file>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 239,
                question: "Extract a tarball (tar.gz):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["tar -xvzf <file.tar.gz>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 240,
                question: "Create a tarball (tar.gz):",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["tar -cvzf <file.tar.gz> <directory>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 241,
                question: "Check system uptime:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["uptime"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 242,
                question: "Reboot the system:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["reboot"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 243,
                question: "Shutdown the system:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["shutdown now"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        topicName: "tmux Commands",
        entries: [
            {
                id: 244,
                question: "Start a new tmux session:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["tmux"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 245,
                question: "Start a new tmux session with a specific name:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["tmux new -s <session-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 246,
                question: "List all tmux sessions:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["tmux ls"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 247,
                question: "Attach to a tmux session:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["tmux attach -t <session-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 248,
                question: "Detach from the current tmux session:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Ctrl-b d"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 249,
                question: "Kill a tmux session:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["tmux kill-session -t <session-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 250,
                question: "Rename the current tmux session:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Ctrl-b $"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 251,
                question: "Create a new window in tmux:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Ctrl-b c"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 252,
                question: "Switch to the next window:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Ctrl-b n"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 253,
                question: "Switch to the previous window:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Ctrl-b p"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 254,
                question: "Switch to a specific window by number:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Ctrl-b <number>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 255,
                question: "Rename the current window:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Ctrl-b ,"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 256,
                question: "Split the current pane horizontally:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Ctrl-b %"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 257,
                question: "Split the current pane vertically:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Ctrl-b \" "],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 258,
                question: "Switch to the next pane:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Ctrl-b o"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 259,
                question: "Resize the current pane:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Ctrl-b <arrow-keys>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 260,
                question: "Close the current pane:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Ctrl-b x"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 261,
                question: "Synchronize panes in tmux:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Ctrl-b : setw synchronize-panes on"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 262,
                question: "Scroll up in the current pane:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["Ctrl-b [ "],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 263,
                question: "Exit scroll mode in tmux:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["q"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 264,
                question: "Save a tmux session to a file:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["tmux save-buffer <file-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 265,
                question: "Restore a tmux session from a file:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["tmux source-file <file-name>"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
            {
                id: 266,
                question: "Kill all tmux sessions:",
                options: [],
                correctAnswer: ["tmux kill-server"],
                inputType: "",
                deepExplanation: "",
                references: [],
            },
        ],
    }
];

